Marching boots lining up in the street.
Broken glass at a three minute speech.
Posters peel but the slogans stay new.
History repeats but the shade is still true.
Sneakers stained with the paint on the walls.
Truth gets lost in a parade of calls.
Length of ocean dressed up for the show.
How much flag do you need just to know?
You want red, white, and blue in your bed.
Kiss a flag, let it cover your head Got the stars in your eye, fight on it grew Fifty shades of red White and blue Oh, oh, oh Oh, oh, oh Wave of banners at the mirror every day
Read your legions through the comfort on display Shaded creed upon the rush of being right Wrapped so tight you can't see a light Disallimated every anthem played Worship power like a game you made
You want red, white, and blue in your bed.
Just a flag, but it's over your head.
You got the stars in your eyes, five on eight through.
Fifty shades of red, white, and blue.